(Bernadette:)Let me see the sonogram again.
(Bernadette:)Oh, yeah, that's a good-looking
baby for a little gray blob.
(Howard:)Yeah, we could
name him Blobert.
(Bernadette:)What if it's a girl?
(Howard:)Bloberta.
Or Blobbi with an "I."
(Bernadette:)Are we being silly
not finding out the sex?
(Howard:)Yeah, I was just
thinking the same thing.
(Sheldon:)If you want,
you can find out right now.
- Mm.
- Hmm.
(Bernadette:)The doctor's gone for the
day, so it doesn't matter.
(Raj:)Well, somebody else knows
(Raj:)because they saw it
in the folder.
(Bernadette:)You looked in
our folder?!
(Raj:)It was an accident.
(Raj:)The doctor left
the folder out on her desk.
(Raj:)It's not my fault
I opened it and looked.
(Howard:)So you know the sex
of our baby, and we don't?!
(Raj:)Flip a coin.
You got a fifty-fifty shot.
(Howard:)It's unbelievable.
- God, Raj.
- What?
(Raj:)This is not a problem, okay?
(Raj:)If you don't want to know,
I don't have to tell you.
We don't want you to know!
(Raj:)Okay, well, that's a problem.